Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
This place seems to have a lot of shops.
It'll be worth shopping around.
This is a lively town.
I see a lot of bars.
Oh, right. Frieren, let's go
shopping together later.
This place seems to have
a lot of nice shops.
If you want.
What are you doing, Frieren? Let's go.
Like a fairy tale
It's a sign the story has reached its end
Like a single passage taken from
A journey that was too long
Of the evil that once cast a shadow
Across this land
And the memories of the short journey
With the hero who defeated it
The story ends
And the hero goes to sleep
Leaving this land with
Days of peace and quiet
The passage of time heartlessly
Makes people forget
Even the tracks left behind by his life
Begin to rust
Just the same
Your words and wishes and courage
Are still inside of me
And they live on
We chose the same path
That's all it was supposed to be
Why is it that at some point
I wanted to understand the reason for
The tears that fall down my cheeks
Even now
If I retrace the journey we walked together
Even though you're not there
I know I'll be able to find it
You don't need to be so harsh!
You're always so rude to me!
Do you really hate me that much?
Forget it! I'm going back to my master!
Would it kill her to listen
to me once in a while?
What's all the noise about?
Are the lovebirds fighting?
It's Fern's birthday today,
but Stark didn't get her a present.
Fern is furious.
Hmph.
Honestly, I think you were too harsh today.
You never listen to anything Stark says.
I didn't get her anything either.
Men don't care about little things
like birthdays and anniversaries.
Ow!
Okay, okay. I'll buy you something,
so stop kicking me.
My knees are gonna be sore later.
I feel sorry for Stark.
I'm old enough to let most callousness go,
but girls can make the emotions
of boys his age swing wildly.
I think you should go after him.
Maybe you should go see him.
That's right. Her hair ornament has
a butterfly on it, too.
That's a cute pouch.
You don't like it?
I don't like how accustomed you seem
to the company of women.
I see.
Did you find Stark?
He was in the plaza.
But you couldn't talk to him, huh?
I get it. It's not that you don't like him.
You just don't know how to
interact with boys your age.
Ah, to be young.
No matter. Choose whatever you want.
We can check out other stores, too.
No, it's fine.
Then I'll choose something for you.
Anyway, even if he forgot to get you
a gift, I think you overreacted.
He's not that conscientious.
I doubt he even remembers his own birthday.
You shouldn't blame him.
I gave Mr. Stark a present on his birthday.
Really? Did you choose one with him?
How did you know?
Normally, no one declines when someone
offers to buy them whatever they want.
You must consider it an important memory.
That's why you said no.
I don't know.
I just felt like it.
I see.
Then go apologize to Stark
and pick out a gift with him.
He's just a kid. He's slow on the uptake.
You want to make up with him, don't you?
People won't know how you feel
unless you tell them.
You're right.
I'm heading back to the inn.
Um...
I'm sorry for kicking you.
Mr. Stark.
Fern.
I—
Sorry!
I wanted to choose a gift with you,
since I don't know what you like.
But I thought you'd get upset with me
again if I said that, so I couldn't.
I wouldn't be upset with you.
Mr. Stark, I'm sorry. I was too harsh.
It's fine. I'm used to it.
I'm really sorry.
Let's go.
Okay.
You're spying on them?
That's in poor taste, Frieren.
Same to you, Sein.
Looks like they made up.
You understand relationships better
once you're older.
You start avoiding conflict then.
Those arguments are the
privilege of the young.
That can't have been easy for you, Frieren.
Looking after two kids sounds tough.
What do you mean by
understanding relationships?
So it's three kids.
Fern asked me for advice instead of you.
I wonder who she's comparing me to.
Fern was raised by Heiter.
She shouldn't be comparing me
to such a great priest.
I'd hardly call him great.
He was a drunk and often hungover.
Has he become an undead?
He was picky with his food, too.
Quit it.
And he lied all the time.
I haven't had anything to drink.
He was just a corrupt priest.
You're even more depraved, though.
Sorry about that.
I'm surprised, though.
The Mr. Heiter I remember was
a kind and dependable old man.
Unlike me, he was an ideal grown-up.
Heiter, you've changed.
You've matured.
What are you talking about? I'm an old man.
It happens naturally as people age.
Huh.
I wish I could say that, anyway,
but the truth is, my mind has
hardly changed since I was a child.
I've simply been pretending to be an adult
until I can make it as an ideal grown-up.
I'll probably keep pretending
until the day I die.
Children need grown-ups
for emotional support.
Fern in particular is the hardworking sort.
She needs lots of praise and guidance.
Then who will praise you for
pretending until the day you die?
That's what the Goddess is for,
though I'll have to wait until I go
to heaven to receive my reward.
Then I'll praise you down here.
You will?
But I'm a human. I doubt you
understand how I feel.
How do you intend to praise me?
That was better than I expected.
Frieren, once I go to heaven,
I'll speak with the Goddess for you.
You should be praised by her.
Oh? Then I'll look forward to it.
What do you think you're doing, Frieren?
I think you're a proper adult, Sein.
I would've loved to have
an older woman do this.
You should be glad, then.
Few women are older than me.
Thank you.
There weren't any passenger carriages
around here, so we appreciate it.
We help each other when we're in need.
I'm actually a merchant in the town up ahead.
I run an accessory shop there.
Are you interested?
You're a good salesman.
I'm not too interested, but Fern
likes that kind of thing. Don't you?
Huh?
Did you buy a new bracelet?
Um, this is...
That's a cute design.
I have a ring with the same design.
Himmel gave it to me.
It probably matches yours.
Really?
Now where did I put it?
Huh?
You're so disorganized.
Found it.
Sorry. I let my guard down.
Avian monsters are cunning
and skilled at concealing their mana.
What are we going to do?
Can't we figure something out with flying
magic after defeating the monster?
You can make a carriage levitate, right?
Stark, have you ever seen a flying carriage?
We're in one right now.
This may surprise you, but it's only been
forty years since humankind learned to fly.
Until then, the skies were the
exclusive domain of demons and monsters.
The flying magic we use is
a repurposed demon spell.
Spare me the details and
dumb it down for me.
It means we can't adapt it
because we copied their technique
without understanding
the principles behind it.
Things larger than humans
can only be made to fly briefly.
I see.
We'll have to get out.
I'll fly out with the merchant.
Fern, could you take Sein?
Understood.
I'll get my cargo together.
What about me?
You can jump down.
What are you talking about?
I'm pretty sure that would kill me.
You're a warrior. A fall from
this height won't kill you.
Of course it would kill me!
Don't act like you don't understand that!
That's odd.
Eisen was never injured by
a free fall from any height.
What is wrong with him?
Heiter was appalled.
That just goes to show that Mr. Eisen
was far from normal.
What about levitating the carriage
just before it hits the ground?
I'll need to calculate
if I can stop a free fall.
If I don't reduce the force sufficiently,
we'll be ground into minced meat.
That sounds horrifying!
Either way, we should probably hurry.
This type of monster hunts by
slamming its prey into the ground.
I see.
Well, it's worth a shot.
Don't just drop us!
W-We're alive.
It seems like the plan was a success.
You call that a success?
You call that a plan?
The horse is only slightly injured.
I've finished treating it.
But the carriage is a wreck.
It needs repairs.
Sorry.
No, thank you.
If it'd just been me, I'd be dead.
It'll take a while to fix the carriage.
Huh?
That's odd.
Where did it go?
It's gotten warmer lately.
Should we start dressing lighter?
By the way, Fern, that bracelet...
It was a birthday present from Mr. Stark.
I spent three hours choosing a gift.
You ended up choosing it?
I asked him to choose what he wanted.
Oh, I see.
That must've been difficult, Stark.
Her type is the hardest to deal with.
Yeah.
Will she like this?
I spent three hours gauging her reactions.
I felt like I was dying.
Poor kid.
I can hear everything they're saying.
But...
I'm glad I did, since she likes it.
Anyway, good going, Stark.
I didn't think you knew what you were doing.
That design is of a mirrored lotus.
In the language of flowers,
it means "eternal love."
In this area, people give them
to their lovers.
Mr. Stark?
I-I didn't know!
This is all a misunderstanding.
You think I know the language of flowers?
That's fair enough. You're an idiot, after all.
You're being even harsher than usual!
It's not like you knew either.
Did you say something?
It's nothing.
Should I buy you a replacement?
You put a lot of effort into
choosing this gift for me.
Don't ever say that again.
Sorry.
What is it?
Nothing.
Ms. Frieren.
We've finished repairing the carriage.
We'll depart early tomorrow morning.
I see.
You've been slipping out every night.
What are you looking for?
The ring Himmel gave me.
I'll help.
We'll wait to depart until we've found it.
No.
If I don't find it tonight,
I'll give up on it.
I'm used to losing things.
Besides, that's not the
only thing Himmel gave me.
Wasn't it a mirrored-lotus
design ring like this one?
In the language of flowers,
it means "eternal love."
Does it? I didn't know.
It doesn't matter. I doubt Himmel
knew what it meant either.
Regardless, I'm sure it's important.
Let's look for it together.
You should've told me.
A few people in my village have
lost accessories over the years.
I intended to give you this spell
for finding lost accessories
as a reward for your assistance.
Frieren.
You worked really hard
to defeat the Demon King.
Choose whatever you'd like.
An accessory, huh?
I would've preferred
something from a magic shop.
This one will do.
That was quick. Put more thought into it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Frieren.
Thank you.
Aren't you glad you didn't
give up, Ms. Frieren?
Maybe.
By the way, why are you wearing
a mirrored-lotus bracelet?
Because Mr. Stark is an idiot.
How could you say that?
And you alright
Can you hear me
Trailing along deserted train tracks
Crying excessively
Wanting you to smile
I hold on to memories I'd like to keep fresh
There's something I'd like to tell you
With words more precious than a goodbye
Unremarkable yet special
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
So, if I were to be born again
I would surely choose this place once more
So, if we were to meet again
I'd never let you go, I'd choose the present
Even if no promises were made
Even if I'm lost in days of loneliness
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
I have battle magic, too.
I feel anxious.
He doesn't have his brother's talent.
Yes, Father.
This is starting to look bad.
In any case, it looks like we should hurry.
It's hell.
This smells like trouble.
Let's head to the next village.